<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prediction Of Divorce.</string>
    <string name="choiceLevel_0">Never</string>
    <string name="choiceLevel_1">Hardly</string>
    <string name="choiceLevel_2">Rarely</string>
    <string name="choiceLevel_3">Often</string>
    <string name="choiceLevel_4">Always</string>
    <string name="item_1">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020If one of us apologizes when our discussion deteriorates, the discussion ends.</string>
    <string name="item_2">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know we can ignore our differences, even if things get hard sometimes.</string>
    <string name="item_3">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020We can discuss our relationship from the beginning and correct our mistakes.</string>
    <string name="item_4">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The time I spent with my husband/wife is special for us.</string>
    <string name="item_5">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020We don\'t have time at home as partners.</string>
    <string name="item_6">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020We are like two strangers who share the same environment at home rather than family.</string>
    <string name="item_7">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I enjoy my holidays with my husband/wife.</string>
    <string name="item_8">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I enjoy traveling with my husband/wife.</string>
    <string name="item_9">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I think that one day in the future when I look back, I see that my spouse and I have been in harmony with each other.</string>
    <string name="item_10">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020My spouse and I have similar values in terms of personal freedom</string>
    <string name="item_11">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020My spouse and I have a similar sense of entertainment.</string>
    <string name="item_12">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Our dreams with my spouse are similar and harmonious.</string>
    <string name="item_13">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020We\'re compatible with my spouse about what love should be.</string>
    <string name="item_14">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020We share the same views about being happy in our life with my spouse.</string>
    <string name="item_15">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020My spouse and I have similar ideas about how marriage should be.</string>
    <string name="item_16">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020My spouse and I have similar ideas about how roles should be in marriage.</string>
    <string name="item_17">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020My spouse and I trust each other. </string>
    <string name="item_18">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know exactly what my husband/wife likes.</string>
    <string name="item_19">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know how my spouse wants to be taken care of when she/he is sick.</string>
    <string name="item_20">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know my spouse\'s favorite food.</string>
    <string name="item_21">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I can tell you what kind of stress my spouse is facing in her/his life.</string>
    <string name="item_22">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I have knowledge of my spouse\'s inner world.</string>
    <string name="item_23">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know my spouse\'s basic anxieties.</string>
    <string name="item_24">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know what my spouse\'s current sources of stress are.</string>
    <string name="item_25">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know my spouse\'s hopes and wishes.</string>
    <string name="item_26">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know my spouse very well.</string>
    <string name="item_27">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I know my spouse\'s friends and their social relationships.</string>
    <string name="item_28">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I feel aggressive when I argue with my spouse.</string>
    <string name="item_29">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020When discussing with my spouse, I usually use expressions such as \‘you always\’ or \‘you never\’.</string>
    <string name="item_30">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I can use negative statements about my spouse\'s personality during our discussions.</string>
    <string name="item_31">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I can use offensive expressions during our discussions.</string>
    <string name="item_32">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I can insult my spouse during our discussions.</string>
    <string name="item_33">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I can be humiliating when we discuss.</string>
    <string name="item_34">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020My discussion with my spouse is not calm.</string>
    <string name="item_35">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I hate my spouse\'s way of opening a subject of discussion.</string>
    <string name="item_36">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020When I talk to my spouse about something, my calm suddenly breaks.</string>
    <string name="item_37">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020When I argue with my spouse, ı only go out and I don\'t say a word.</string>
    <string name="item_38">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I mostly stay silent to calm the situation a little bit.</string>
    <string name="item_39">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Sometimes I think it\'s good for me to leave home for a while.</string>
    <string name="item_40">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I\'d rather stay silent than discuss it with my spouse.</string>
    <string name="item_41">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020When I discuss with my spouse, I stay silent because I am afraid of not being able to control my anger.</string>
    <string name="item_42">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I feel right in our discussions.</string>
    <string name="item_43">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I have nothing to do with what I\'ve been accused of.</string>
    <string name="item_44">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I\'m not actually the one who\'s guilty about what I\'m accused of.</string>
    <string name="item_45">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I\'m not the one who\'s wrong about problems at home.</string>
    <string name="item_46">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020I\'m not afraid to tell my spouse about her/his incompetence.</string>
    <string name="title_result">Your Result is...</string>
    <string name="predict_yes_result">You will be divorce.</string>
    <string name="predict_no_result">You will not be divorce.</string>
    <string name="home_button">Back to HOME MENU</string>
    <string name="song_paragraph">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Looking for that perfect song to play for your next romantic evening? Maybe you have a special date coming up, or an anniversary, or want to choose just the right music for Valentine\'s Day? Here is a list of some of the best love songs to help you create a great playlist for your special date.</string>
    <string name="song_1" translatable="false">"Yellow" - Coldplay</string>
    <string name="song_2" translatable="false">"Lover" - Taylor Swift</string>
    <string name="song_3" translatable="false">"No One" - Alicia Keys</string>
    <string name="song_4" translatable="false">"Ocean" - Lady Antebellum</string>
    <string name="song_5" translatable="false">"Wife You Up" - Russ</string>
    <string name="song_6" translatable="false">"The Bones" - Maren Morris</string>
    <string name="song_7" translatable="false">"Love Song" - Lana Del Rey</string>
    <string name="song_8" translatable="false">"You and I Both" - Jason Mraz</string>
    <string name="song_9" translatable="false">"When I Look At You" - Miley Cyrus</string>
    <string name="song_10" translatable="false">"She Will Be Loved" - Maroon 5</string>
    <string name="song_11" translatable="false">"Kiss Me" - Ed Sheeran</string>
    <string name="song_12" translatable="false">"All of Me" - John Legend</string>
    <string name="song_13" translatable="false">"At Last" - Etta James</string>
    <string name="song_14" translatable="false">"Just the Way You Are" - Bruno Mars</string>
    <string name="song_15" translatable="false">"Perfect" - Ed Sheeran ft. Beyoncé</string>
    <string name="song_16" translatable="false">"Halo" - Beyoncé</string>
    <string name="song_17" translatable="false">"Thinking Out Loud" - Ed Sheeran</string>
    <string name="song_18" translatable="false">"Love on the Brain" - Rihanna</string>
    <string name="des_song_1" translatable="false">Look at the stars\nLook how they shine for you\nAnd everything you do\nYeah they were all yellow..."</string>
    <string name="des_song_2" translatable="false">My heart\'s been borrowed and yours has been blue\nAll\'s well that ends well to end up with you...</string>
    <string name="des_song_3" translatable="false">You and me together\nThrough the days and nights\nI don\'t worry \'cause\nEverything\'s gonna be alright...</string>
    <string name="des_song_4" translatable="false">Here you are, next to me\nSo much beauty at my feet\nAll I wanna do is swim\nBut the waves keep crashin\' in...</string>
    <string name="des_song_5" translatable="false">I\'m turning down the rest for you\nIf they call us foul I\'m fighting all the refs for you\nYou make me a better me\nI make you a better you....</string>
    <string name="des_song_6" translatable="false">Call it dumb luck, but baby, you and I\nCan\'t even mess it up, although we both try\nNo, it don\'t always go the way we planned it\nBut the wolves came and went and we\'re still standing...</string>
    <string name="des_song_7" translatable="false">Oh, be my once in a lifetime\nLyin\' on your chest in my party dress\nI\'m a fuckin\' mess, but I\nOh, thanks for the high life...</string>
    <string name="des_song_8" translatable="false">And it\'s okay if you have to go away\nOh just remember the telephones, well they work in both ways\nBut if I never ever hear them ring\nIf nothing else I\'ll think the bells inside\nHave finally found you someone else and that\'s okay\n\'Cause I\'ll remember everything you sang...</string>
    <string name="des_song_9" translatable="false">When I look at you, I see forgiveness\nI see the truth\nYou love me for who I am\nLike the stars hold the moon\nRight there where they belong\nAnd I know I\'m not alone...</string>
    <string name="des_song_10" translatable="false">I don\'t mind spendin\' everyday\nOut on your corner in the pourin\' rain\nLook for the girl with the broken smile\nAsk her if she wants to stay awhile\nAnd she will be loved, and she will be loved...</string>
    <string name="des_song_11" translatable="false">And your heart\'s against my chest\nYour lips pressed in my neck\nI\'m falling for your eyes, but they don\'t know me yet\nAnd with a feeling I\'ll forget, I\'m in love now...</string>
    <string name="des_song_12" translatable="false">Cause all of me\nLoves all of you\nLove your curves and all your edges\nAll your perfect imperfections...</string>
    <string name="des_song_13" translatable="false">At last my love has come along\nMy lonely days are over\nAnd life is like a song...</string>
    <string name="des_song_14" translatable="false">Oh, you know, you know, you know I\'d never ask you to change\nIf perfect\'s what you\'re searching for, then just stay the same...</string>
    <string name="des_song_15" translatable="false">I\'m dancing in the dark\nWith you between my arms\nBarefoot on the grass\nWhile listening to our favorite song...</string>
    <string name="des_song_16" translatable="false">Hit me like a ray of sun\nBurning through my darkest night\nYou\'re the only one that I want\nThink I\'m addicted to your light...</string>
    <string name="des_song_17" translatable="false">But baby now\nTake me into your loving arms\nKiss me under the light of a thousand stars.</string>
    <string name="des_song_18" translatable="false">Must be love on the brain\nThat\'s got me feeling this way\nIt beats me black and blue but it fucks me so good\nAnd I can\'t get enough...</string>
    <string name="home_predict" >Predict Divorce</string>
    <string name="home_sub_predict" >Let\'s Predict</string>
    <string name="home_lovesong" >Love Song</string>
    <string name="home_sub_lovesong" >Great Love Songs for Your Romantic Playlist</string>
    <string name="home_tenthingcheating" >10 Things to Do Immediately When You Find Out Your Partner Is Cheating</string>
    <string name="home_sub_tenthingcheating" >This is some information for you how to do when you found that he/she is cheating on you.</string>
    <string name="home_eightstep" >8 Steps That Can Save Your Marriage from Divorce</string>
    <string name="home_sub_eightstep" >The ways you to treat yourself for saving your marriage.</string>

    <string name="movie_n1" translatable="false">Titanic (1997)</string>
    <string name="movie_1">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Titanic has all the makings of a boilerplate love story: Jack (Leonardo DiCaprio) is from the wrong side of the tracks, Rose (Kate Winslet) comes from high society, and they meet by chance and fall in love. But set against the spectacle of the sinking of the historic ship — and with greatest-love-song-of-all-time contender "My Heart Will Go On" in the background — like Jack, this movie moves beyond its seemingly plain origins.</string>
    <string name="movie_n2" translatable="false">Before Sunrise (1995)</string>
    <string name="movie_2">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Director Richard Linklater pulls of a remarkable feat with this casual film: the entire relationship unfolds as the two main characters walk around a European city, just chatting. It proves that great romances don\'t have to be so emotionally wrought. The film spawned two sequels, Before Sunset and Before Midnight, which follow the same couple.</string>
    <string name="movie_n3" translatable="false">Portrait of a Lady on Fire (2019)</string>
    <string name="movie_3">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020This film-festival favorite, which was nominated for a slew of awards at the end of 2019, follows a woman who is commissioned to travel to a remote island to paint a portrait of a woman as part of an arranged marriage; of course, she falls in love with her subject, and a forbidden romance ensues.</string>
    <string name="movie_n4" translatable="false">A Star Is Born (2018)</string>
    <string name="movie_4">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020If you\'re looking for a story about people brought together by talent and torn apart by fame, you can watch a number of takes on A Star Is Born: There\'s the 1937 original with Janet Gaynor and Fredric March, the 1954 version with Judy Garland and James Mason, and the 1976 remake with Barbra Streisand and Kris Kristofferson. But only the most recent one, with Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper, has a performance of the heart-rending song "Shallow."</string>
    <string name="movie_n5" translatable="false">If Beale Street Could Talk (2018)</string>
    <string name="movie_5">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020"From Barry Jenkins — director of Moonlight, which is its own sort of romance — comes this James Baldwin adaptation. It's about a couple, madly in love and expecting a child, whose relationship is upended when one of them is accused of a crime he didn't commit.</string>
    <string name="movie_n6" translatable="false">Shape of Water (2017)</string>
    <string name="movie_6">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020If you know anything about Guillermo del Toro, then you know better than to ever try to predict what the fantastical director’s take on a love story would be. Besides, of course, that it will be more beautiful and unique than you could ever imagine. Shape of Water tells the tale of Elisa, a mute woman who works as a cleaning lady at a government laboratory, as she finds herself falling in love with the lab’s top-secret specimen: an amphibious creature. This film is a true testament that love comes in all shapes and sizes.</string>
    <string name="movie_n7" translatable="false">The Big Sick (2017)</string>
    <string name="movie_7">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Kumail Nanjiani and Emily V. Gordon’s real-life hospital romance turned movie is one of the most original and thoughtful romances in years. In the face of tragedy, an estranged couple grows closer somehow by one of them being in a coma. Also, Holly Hunter is the best mom.</string>
    <string name="movie_n8" translatable="false">Silver Linings Playbook (2012)</string>
    <string name="movie_8">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The first real entry of the Cooper/Lawrence film trio, Silver Linings Playbook is the story of what happens when perfectly flawed people find love together. The film also won Lawrence her first Oscar, and that’s pretty outstanding for a picture loosely categorized as a romantic comedy.</string>
    <string name="movie_n9" translatable="false">The Notebook (2004)</string>
    <string name="movie_9">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Read me this story, and I’ll find you. Damn. Nicholas Sparks is cheesy and oftentimes over the top, but The Notebook is a romantic story of love that just beautiful enough that it transcends all of the cheesiness it takes to tell it.</string>
    <string name="movie_n10" translatable="false">Call Me By Your Name (2017)</string>
    <string name="movie_10">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020That peach scene is something else. The Luca Guadagnino-directed film perfectly encapsulates the feelings of first love and love lost in a beautiful Italian setting. Bonus points: CMBYN is the rare gay love story where someone doesn’t get beaten or end up with HIV.</string>


</resources>
